<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">GNR</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">90\'s Grunge Sensation</string>
    <string name="article_text"><b>Gun n roses</b>
        Guns N Roses, often abbreviated as GNR, is an American hard rock band from Los Angeles,
        California, formed in 1985. When they signed to Geffen Records in 1986, the band
        comprised vocalist Axl Rose, lead guitarist Slash, rhythm guitarist Izzy Stradlin,
        bassist Duff McKagan, and drummer Steven Adler. The current lineup consists of Rose,
        Slash, McKagan, guitarist Richard Fortus, drummer Frank Ferrer and keyboardists Dizzy Reed and Melissa Reese.
        \n \n
        In the late 1980s, GNR established itself as part of the Seattle https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grunge scene, releasing its first album,
        Bleach, for the independent record label Sub Pop in 1989. They developed a sound that relied on dynamic contrasts,
        often between quiet verses and loud, heavy choruses. After signing to major label DGC Records in 1991, Nirvana found unexpected mainstream success with https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smells_Like_Teen_Spirit,
        the first single from their landmark second album Nevermind (1991). A cultural phenomenon of the 1990s,
        the album went on to be certified Diamond by the RIAA and is often credited for ending the dominance of hair metal.
        \n \n
    Characterized by their punk aesthetic, fusion of pop melodies with noise, combined with their themes of abjection and social alienation,
        brought them global popularity. Following extensive tours and the 1992 compilation album Incesticide and EP Hormoaning,
        the band released their abrasive and less mainstream sounding third studio album, In Utero (1993). The album topped both the US and UK album charts, and was acclaimed by critics.
        Nirvana disbanded following Cobain\'s suicide in April 1994. Various posthumous releases have been overseen by Novoselic, Grohl, and Cobain\'s widow Courtney Love.
        The posthumous live album MTV Unplugged in New York (1994) won Best Alternative Music Performance at the 1996 Grammy Awards.
        \n \n
        By 2009, record sales were over 75 million worldwide, making them one of the best-selling bands of all time. During their three years as a mainstream act,
        Nirvana received an American Music Award, Brit Award and Grammy Award, as well as seven MTV Video Music Awards and two NME Awards.
        They achieved five number-one hits on the Billboard Alternative Songs chart and four number-one albums on the Billboard 200. In 2004,
        Rolling Stone named  among the 100 greatest artists of all time. They were inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in their first year of eligibility in 2014.
    </string>
    <string name="add_comment">Add comment</string>
</resources>